<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bythos</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Bythos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 19:15:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OME FlatBT</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/preamplifiers/flatbt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 19:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/preamplifiers/flatbt/</guid><description>High Audiophile Grade LINE Preamplifier FlatBT is our answer to the growing demand for high-end preamplifiers from the audiophile and DIY community. In most cases, audiophiles look for linear stages with wide bandwidth and flat frequency response without any tone controls, as well as with very low output impedance for easy connection to modern output amplifiers. FlatBT was designed following such requirements and we believe that it will more than meet all reasonable expectations of even the most discerning and demanding audiophiles.</description></item><item><title>Sipi Shunt PSU</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/psus/sipi-shunt-psu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:46:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/psus/sipi-shunt-psu/</guid><description>High Class Shunt PSU SIPI SHUNT psu is designed to be applied as an upgrade in analog and digital playback equipment like (SA)CD players, DACs, PREAMPs and alike. The shunts drop in instead of commonly used industrial types of regulators. Having much lower noise, true wide bandwidth and linear output impedance, they&amp;rsquo;ll bring improvement to sound in terms of:
higher resolution better transparency clean low ends increased dynamics Traditionally, voltage regulators never where designed for audio applications.</description></item><item><title>Soft Start</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/protections/softstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 12:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/protections/softstart/</guid><description>Protects Your Fuses And Toroids THIS CIRCUIT ensures that excessive current surges do not occur when the mains voltage is switched on.
Basically, the unit provides the following features:
It protects fuses against excessive current surges - eq. when power on It provides ON/OFF momentary push button to turn ON or OFF toroidal transformers It provides power on delay and four 5W resistors to limit current surges Its operation is simple, and is based on the fact that the current is initially limited by R4-R7 immediately after switch-on.</description></item><item><title>Speaker Protection</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/protections/speaker-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 10:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/protections/speaker-protection/</guid><description>Protects Your Precious Speakers ALTHOUGH DESIGNED specifically for our Class-A Stereo Amplifer, this unit can actually be used with any audio amplifer with supply rails up to about 70V DC, simply by selecting two resistor values to suit.
Basically, the unit provides the following features:
It protects the loudspeakers against catastrophic failure in the amplifier – eg, if an output transistor goes short circuit It provides muting at switch-on and switch-off, to prevent thumps from the loudspeakers It provides an input for an over-temperature switch to disconnect the loudspeakers if the output stage heat-sink temperature rises above a certain level.</description></item><item><title>Bythos</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/amplifiers/bythos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/amplifiers/bythos/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Simulation</title><link>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/tutorials/simulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ronovar.github.io/bythos.github.io/tutorials/simulation/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>